Finding Aid for Ernest T. Campbell sermons, 1963-1968
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Ernest T. Campbell sermons 1963-1968
Campbell, Ernest T.
29 items
755 DA 2; C187.5; S486
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was received from Dr. Campbell (donor no. 4655 ).
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Dr. Ernest T. Campbell was minister at the First Presbyterian Church of Ann Arbor, Michigan during the 1960s.
The collection consists of published sermons preached by Dr. Ernest T. Campbell, April 14, 1963-April 28, 1968
Subjects:
Sermons, American.; First Presbyterian Church (Ann Arbor, Mich.)
- Sermons
  - Christ is Risen!--Christ is Here! April 14, 1963 (Box 1)
  - A Christian and his City. April 28, 1963 (Box 1)
  - People, Property and Jesus. September 15, 1963 (Box 1)
  - That Man at My Gate. October 20, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Grace Relations. February 9, 1964 (Box 1)
  - In the Meantime. September 13, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Stones are not Enough. October 11, 1964 (Box 1)
  - The Best is Yet To Be. January 10, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Too Good for God! October 10, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Not to be Ministered Unto But to Minister. December 19, 1965 (Box 1)
  - The Claims of Christ and Caesar. February 13, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Easter Makes It All Worthwhile! April 10, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Responsibility-The Forgotten Word. April 24, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Jesus' Summary of the Law. May 8, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Standing By. August 14, 1966 (Box 1)
  - His Kingdom Cannot Fail. September 11, 1966 (Box 1)
  - On Learning Who We Are. December 18, 1966 (Box 1)
  - The Depletion Anxiety. January 1, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Loyalties Under Fire I Worship January 15, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Loyalties Under Fire II Prayer January 29, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Loyalties Under Fire III Fixed Rules of Conduct February 19, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Loyalties Under Fire IV Chastity February 26, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Loyalties Under Fire V The Missionary Enterprise March 5, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Loyalties Under Fire VI Preaching March 12, 1967 (Box 1)
  - God's Little People. June 18, 1967 (Box 1)
  - The End Toward Which We Move. September 24, 1967 (Box 1)
  - The Christian and his Country. November 19, 1967 (Box 1)
  - On Being Approachable. February 25, 1968 (Box 1)
  - The Ministry of Rebuke. April 28, 1968 (Box 1)